<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Tushar's blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[My thoughts and learnings.]]></description><link>https://sadh.life/rss.xml</link><item><title><![CDATA[The math behind Python's slices]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/slices/</link><description><![CDATA[You can pass negative indices to Python slices?! Learn about them and a lot more in this guide.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[What the f-strings?]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/what-the-f-strings/</link><description><![CDATA[A comprehensive overview of Python's hottest new feature: f-strings.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ace your leetcode preparations]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/leetcode-prep/</link><description><![CDATA[The things I made and tips I learned while practicing my Data Structures and Algorithms on LeetCode.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Comprehensive Guide to mypy]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/mypy-guide/</link><description><![CDATA[A single article to teach you everything you need to know about Python's type checker.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Python need types?]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/does-python-need-types/</link><description><![CDATA[Python is famously a dynamic language, and many attribute its success to its dynamically typed nature. But is that really all there is to it?]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[Connecting android apps to localhost, simplified]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/android-localhost/</link><description><![CDATA[Figure out how to setup your android development environment, the right way.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to setup PostgreSQL on Manjaro linux / Arch]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/setup-postgres/</link><description><![CDATA[This guide is here just because I’ve messed up the installs on arch before, and turns out it’s actually pretty easy to do.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[How I made my own URL shortener for free]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/url-shortener/</link><description><![CDATA[It's quick, it's easy, and it's free! Oh, and it's actually pretty useful and clever.]]></description></item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding all of Python, through its builtins]]></title><link>https://sadh.life/post/builtins/</link><description><![CDATA[Python has a whole lot of builtins that are unknown to most people. This guide aims to introduce you to everything that Python has to offer, through its seemingly obscure builtins.]]></description></item></channel></rss>